https://www.caryortho.com/privacy-policy/

Skip to content Privacy Policyadmin2020-10-21T20:39:05+00:00PRIVACY POLICYCary Orthopaedics is committed to honoring the privacy of our patients. Accordingly, we adhere to the following privacy policies as they relate to our website.Information Collection and UseWe do not collect any personal information about our website visitors other than that which you provide to us. Please note that the appointment request form on our main website is not privacy protected; therefore, providing health information via the form is solely at the discretion of the patient.We are the sole owners of the information collected through our website. We only have access to information that you voluntarily give us via email, online forms, or other direct contact from you. We do not sell, trade, exchange or otherwise make available any personally identifiable information to any other company or organization. We do not collect financial information from consumers viewing this website. We keep track of the websites and pages our clients visit within the Cary Orthopaedics website in order to determine what services are most in demand.External LinksThis site contains an external link to our Patient Portal. Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as health history and credit card data) that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure manner.This site may contain links to other external sites that we believe to be helpful and informative to our clients. Cary Orthopaedics is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of other such sites. We encourage our users, when they leave our site, to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.For more information about our commitment to your privacy, please see our HIPAA Privacy Policy.
Go to Top
